#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jimmywangkhem-31940422 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Management Recruiting Leadership

### Certifications

Accessibility in Action

# Jimmy Wangkhem

Recruiter at Microsoft

Bengaluru

## Summary

I am a technical Recruiter with extensive experience in building strong technology teams from scratch for product development companies. Skilled in souring passive talent for product development skills through various social media channels.

ALWAYS OPEN TO TALK /CONNECT WITH NEW PEOPLE ABOUT NEW IDEAS AND NEW TECHNOLOGIES.

## Experience

Microsoft

Recruiter

February 2016 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Currently working for Microsoft India Development Center (IDC) Engineering group for different levels of positions and handling end to end recruitment cycle.

Responsibilities:

- o Maintaining relationships with top business stakeholders on hiring top engineers from different tech domains.
- o Offer Management.
- o Hands-on experience in Data Management, weekly status reports and drive business meetings successfully.
- o Talent mapping and market intelligence reports.
- o Sourcing by gathering a good amount of market intelligence to hire bestqualified candidates to Microsoft IDC.
- o Mentoring core Talent Sourcer and ensure they deliver as per business demands.

Sutherland Global Services
Consultant
January 2014 - December 2015 (2 years)
Page 1 of 2

Hyderabad Area, India

Tata Business Support Services Limited Customer Support Executive June 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 7 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

## Education

WLC College India Ltd.

PGDM, Human Resources Management and Services · (2009 - 2011)